Guide to the Al Qassim Family Collection of photographs AD.MC.031
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Al Qassim Family Collection Prints, 11758 (Object AD_MC_031_ref168)
  - Dubai Airport's old building. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9677; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref82)
    Cars/Trucks; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation; Buildings
  - Man in front of Dubai Airport's main entrance. 6.2 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9678; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref83)
    Airports; Men; Doors/Entrances; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Dubai's old airport. 6.1 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9679; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref84)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airports; Buildings
  - A building in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9680; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref85)
    Architecture; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - Customs point of Khor Dubai. 5.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9681; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref86)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Water
  - Khatt Fort, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.5 cm, 8 March 1962; 9682; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref87)
    Mountains/Hills; Forts/Castles; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Landscape of houses by the ocean. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9683; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref88)
    Landscapes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Beaches; Houses; Water; Buildings; Architecture
  - Dubai Landscape. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9684; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref89)
    Houses; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Buildings
  - View of houses in Bur Dubai. 6.2 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 9685; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref90)
    Landscapes; Architecture; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - Landscape of Dubai. 6.8 x 8.8, Undated; 9686; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref91)
    Water; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Buildings; Landscapes; Architecture; Buildings
  - Landscape view of Bur Dubai. 6.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9687; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref92)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Buildings
  - View of Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9727; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref93)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water; Buildings; Houses
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 9728; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref94)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Landscapes; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Water
  - Landscape of Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9729; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref95)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Water; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Houses; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing
  - Landscape view of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; 9730; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref96)
    Landscapes; Architecture; Construction; Water; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Ports; Arabic Writing; Houses; Buildings
  - View of Khor Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9731; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref97)
    Water; Buildings; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Houses at the edge of Khor Dubai. 6.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; 9732; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref98)
    Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Landscapes; Architecture; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Buildings
  - Umm Al-Quwain from a far. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965; 9733; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref99)
    Landscapes; Buildings; Water; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of mountains in Masafi, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, 25 February 1965; 9734; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref100)
    Outdoors; Palm Trees; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Animals; Agriculture/Farms; Mountains/Hills
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9735; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref101)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Landscapes; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - Landscape of the desert in Al-Dhaid. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9736; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref102)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Landscapes; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints
  - Al-Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.4 x 8.7, Undated; 9737; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref103)
    Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of Al-Salehia. 6.4 x 6.7 cm, Undated; 9738; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref104)
    Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Landscapes
  - View of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9739; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref105)
    Outdoors; Agriculture/Farms; Arabic Writing; Landscapes; Houses; Outdoors; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture
  - Mushrif Area, Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9740; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref106)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Landscapes; Outdoors
  - Al-Dhaid desert, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9741; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref107)
    Deserts; Outdoors; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors
  - Farm in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9742; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref108)
    Outdoors; Agriculture/Farms; Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9743; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref109)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Deserts; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Outdoors; Arabic Writing
  - Shinas, Oman. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9744; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref110)
    Oman; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Al Kharran desert in Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9746; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref111)
    Outdoors; Deserts; Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Man in front of the sea with Umm Al-Quwain in the background. 6.8 x 9.0 cm, 25 February 1965; 9747; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref112)
    Landscapes; Men; Water; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Beaches; Umm Al-Quwain, United Arab Emirates; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Al-Salehia desert, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9748; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref113)
    Countryside/Rural; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Deserts
  - Desert in Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9749; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref114)
    Landscapes; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A goat in an old house in Deira, Dubai. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Circa 1960-1969; 9750; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref115)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Houses; Animals; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Goats
  - Official portrait of Sabah Salem Al Mubarak Al Sabah Emir of Kuwait. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated; 9751; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref116)
    Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Officials
  - Portrait of Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum. 8.8 x 6.7 cm, Undated; 9752; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref117)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Officials; Men
  - Men and boys walking during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai airport. 4.9 x 7.1 cm, Undated; 9753; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref118)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Boys; Men
  - Group of men waiting during Sheikh Rashid's reception at the Dubai Airport. 5.2 x 7.3 cm, Undated; 9754; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref119)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - View of Khor Dubai from above. 6.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated; 9755; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref120)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Architecture; Houses
  - Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, 8 March 1962; 9756; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref121)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Animals; Deserts; Outdoors; Outdoors; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Photographic Prints
  - Group of men in the Al Kharran desert. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, 8 March 1962; 9757; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref122)
    Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Countryside/Rural; Outdoors; Deserts; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - Group of men welcoming Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.0 x 7.1 cm, Undated; 9758; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref123)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Men; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Men greeting Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.3 x 7.4 cm, Undated; 9759; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref124)
    Regional/National Dress; Crowds; Sheikhs; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men
  - Boys swimming in Khatt Spring, Ras Al Khaimah. 6.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; 9760; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref125)
    Palm Trees; Outdoors; Springs; Water; Men; Boys; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Farm in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9761; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref126)
    Outdoors; Palm Trees; Agriculture/Farms; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - A man shaking hands with Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.1 cm, Undated; 9762; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref127)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Men
  - A group of men at the Dubai Aiport for Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.3 x 7.2 cm, Undated; 9763; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref128)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Regional/National Dress; Cars/Trucks; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation
  - A group of men disembarking an Iran Air plane at the Dubai Airport. 5.1 x 7.3, Undated; 9764; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref129)
    Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Iran; Airplanes; Airports
  - Group of men at the Dubai Aiport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's Reception. 5.3 x 7.3 cm, 1965; 9765; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref130)
    Sheikhs; Crowds; Regional/National Dress; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men
  - A man holding a child at the Dubai Airport during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception. 5.1 x 7.2 cm, Undated; 9766; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref131)
    Boys; Children; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sheikhs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Airports
  - Date palm trees in Filli, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9767; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref132)
    Countryside/Rural; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees
  - Two men in Khatt, Ras Al Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.6 cm, Undated; 9768; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref133)
    Agriculture/Farms; Cameras; Men; Water; Irrigation; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees
  - Boys by the irrigation system in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9769; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref134)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Water; Agriculture/Farms; Irrigation; Boys; Outdoors
  - Desert of Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9770; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref135)
    Deserts; Outdoors; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural
  - Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9771; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref136)
    Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 9772; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref137)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Countryside/Rural; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors
  - Men working on a construction in Al-Dhaid. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9773; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref138)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Construction; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Men
  - Boy posing behind tobacco plants in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.7 x 6.2 cm, Undated; 9774; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref139)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Deserts; Outdoors; Boys; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - Two men next to a truck in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9900; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref140)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - View from a mosque in Khor Dubai. 6.4 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9901; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref141)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Water
  - Landscape of Dubai from above. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9902; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref142)
    Buildings; Houses; Palm Trees; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Landscapes; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Landscape of Al-Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9903; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref143)
    Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Countryside/Rural; Deserts
  - View of houses in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9904; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref144)
    Architecture; Buildings; Houses; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - View of Dubai from Bur Dubai. 6.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 9905; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref145)
    Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Landscapes
  - View of the Arabian Gulf, Dubai. 6.7 x 8.6 cm, 25 August 1964; 9906; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref146)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Boats/Ships; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Water; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - Men inside tent in Al Salehia, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 9907; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref147)
    Deserts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Tents; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Mountains in Masafi, Dubai. 6.8 x 8.9 cm, 25 February 1965; 9908; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref148)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Palm Trees; Mountains/Hills; Arabic Writing; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates
  - Group of men on a trip in Al Kharran, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 9909; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref149)
    Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Men; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Tents
  - Crowd surrounding a car during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9911; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref150)
    Crowds; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Cars/Trucks; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Transportation
  - Two boys in front of a tent in Al Dhaid, Sharjah. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 9953; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref151)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Tents; Men; Boys
  - Landscape of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 10003; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref152)
    Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Palm Trees; Houses; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Deserts; Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings
  - A car in front of a crowd of men during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 8.8 x 6.6 cm, Undated; 10079; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref153)
    Sheikhs; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Regional/National Dress; Airports; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Transportation
  - A minaret of a mosque in Dubai. 6.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; 10124; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref154)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Architecture; Religious Sites
  - A water tank in Dubai. 6.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; 10149; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref155)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Water
  - View of stores in Deira, Dubai. 6.3 x 9.0 cm, Undated; 10197; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref156)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Shops; Buildings; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - Men swimming in the hot springs in Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; 10215; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref157)
    Swimming; Springs; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Men; Water; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Landscape of the coast of Oman. 8.8 x 6.8 cm, Undated; 10216; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref158)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Seas; Oman; Coast; Beaches; Landscapes
  - Man inside tower of Khatt, Ras Al-Khaimah. 8.6 x 6.7 cm, 25 August 1964; 10218; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref159)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Arabic Writing; Architecture
  - Crowd of people during Sheikh Rashid Al Maktoum's reception at the Dubai Airport. 6.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; 10219; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref160)
    Sheikhs; Airports; Audiences/Spectators; Regional/National Dress; Men; Crowds; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Police; Boys; Dubai, United Arab Emirates
  - View of the sea on the road between Dubai and Ras Al-Khaimah. 6.7 x 8.7, Undated; 10220; Al Qasim, Abdulghafoor, Mr. (Object AD_MC_031_ref161)
    Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Water; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Beaches; Seas
- Al Qassim Family Slides